Ever have the feeling that... you're not alone?
You're Not Alone is a thriller, horror film directed by Eduardo Rodríguez.
After the premature death of her estranged husband, Emma (Winter) regains custody of their young
daughter Isla (Jones) and hopes to rebuild their relationship after many years apart.
But when an evil entity begins to torment them, mother and daughter are forced to face
the inexplicable presence that inhabits the walls of their new home.
Emma, played by Katia Winter.
The Lawyer, played by Martin Barabas.
Teacher, played by Julee Cerda.
Mark, played by Zach Avery.
Assistant to Father Walsh, played by Bettina Skye.
Father Walsh, played by Richard Bekins.
You're Not Alone or You Are Not Alone may refer to:
The film explores themes of supernatural, house, new
home, entity, mother daughter relationship.
The tone is dark and intense.